{
    "subject": "resource/\u00c7a\u011flar_Birinci",
    "predicate": "ontology/careerStation",
    "object": "resource/\u00c7a\u011flar_Birinci__6",
    "human_readable": "\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career station is \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.985428512096405,
            "question": "What is \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9666864275932312,
            "question": "Could \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6 be a job title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9589718580245972,
            "question": "What does \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6 refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.958342969417572,
            "question": "What kind of information might be associated with \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9533911943435669,
            "question": "Does \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci hold multiple career stations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9284446835517883,
            "question": "Is \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci employed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9196116924285889,
            "question": "What other details about \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career might exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8921703696250916,
            "question": "What are some possible interpretations of '\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8913792371749878,
            "question": "How could we find more information about \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42593225836753845,
            "question": "Is there a hierarchy implied by the term 'career station'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career station is \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4204_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How could we find more information about \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4204_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some possible interpretations of '\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4204_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other details about \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career might exist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4204_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4204_51.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4204/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt contains information about Caglar Hepterlikci, but it does not mention anything about a career station called \"\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6\" associated with him."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe provided documents do not contain any information related to \"\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci's career station being \u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6\" or any similar information. The closest relevant information is about Caglar Hepterlikci, a guitarist and music producer, but there are no details about his professional title being \"\u00c7a\u011flar Birinci-6.\" Therefore, the answer is \"no.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}